[
    {
        "sectionId": 0,
        "entities": [
            {
                "id": 0,
                "startChar": 0,
                "endChar": 5,
                "label": "ORG",
                "text": "Apple"
            },
            {
                "id": 1,
                "startChar": 27,
                "endChar": 31,
                "label": "GPE",
                "text": "U.K"
            },
            {
                "id": 2,
                "startChar": 44,
                "endChar": 54,
                "label": "MONEY",
                "text": "$1 billion"
            },
            {
                "id": 3,
                "startChar": 57,
                "endChar": 62,
                "label": "ORG",
                "text": "Apple"
            },
            {
                "id": 4,
                "startChar": 84,
                "endChar": 88,
                "label": "GPE",
                "text": "U.K"
            },
            {
                "id": 5,
                "startChar": 101,
                "endChar": 111,
                "label": "MONEY",
                "text": "$1 billion"
            },
            {
                "id": 6,
                "startChar": 114,
                "endChar": 119,
                "label": "ORG",
                "text": "Apple"
            },
            {
                "id": 7,
                "startChar": 141,
                "endChar": 145,
                "label": "GPE",
                "text": "U.K"
            },
            {
                "id": 8,
                "startChar": 158,
                "endChar": 168,
                "label": "MONEY",
                "text": "$1 billion"
            }
        ],
        "sents": [
            {
                "id": 0,
                "startChar": 0,
                "endChar": 57,
                "prob": 0.43119,
                "text": "Apple is looking at buying U.K. startup for $1 billion."
            },
            {
                "id": 1,
                "startChar": 57,
                "endChar": 114,
                "prob": 0.22251,
                "text": "Apple is looking at buying U.K. startup for $2 billion"
            },
            {
                "id": 2,
                "startChar": 114,
                "endChar": 169,
                "prob": 0.15779,
                "text": "Apple is looking at buying U.K. startup for $3 billion"
            }
        ],
        "text": "Apple is looking at buying U.K. startup for $1 billion.\r\nApple is looking at buying U.K. startup for $2 billion.\r\nApple is looking at buying U.K. startup for $3 billion."
    },
    {
        "sectionId": 1,
        "entities": [
            {
                "id": 0,
                "startChar": 0,
                "endChar": 5,
                "label": "ORG",
                "text": "Apple"
            },
            {
                "id": 1,
                "startChar": 27,
                "endChar": 31,
                "label": "GPE",
                "text": "U.K"
            },
            {
                "id": 2,
                "startChar": 44,
                "endChar": 54,
                "label": "MONEY",
                "text": "$1 billion"
            },
            {
                "id": 3,
                "startChar": 57,
                "endChar": 62,
                "label": "ORG",
                "text": "Apple"
            },
            {
                "id": 4,
                "startChar": 84,
                "endChar": 88,
                "label": "GPE",
                "text": "U.K"
            },
            {
                "id": 5,
                "startChar": 101,
                "endChar": 111,
                "label": "MONEY",
                "text": "$1 billion"
            },
            {
                "id": 6,
                "startChar": 114,
                "endChar": 119,
                "label": "ORG",
                "text": "Apple"
            },
            {
                "id": 7,
                "startChar": 141,
                "endChar": 145,
                "label": "GPE",
                "text": "U.K"
            },
            {
                "id": 8,
                "startChar": 158,
                "endChar": 168,
                "label": "MONEY",
                "text": "$1 billion"
            }
        ],
        "sents": [
            {
                "id": 0,
                "startChar": 0,
                "endChar": 57,
                "prob": 0.43119,
                "text": "Apple is looking at buying U.K. startup for $1 billion."
            },
            {
                "id": 1,
                "startChar": 57,
                "endChar": 114,
                "prob": 0.22251,
                "text": "Apple is looking at buying U.K. startup for $2 billion"
            },
            {
                "id": 2,
                "startChar": 114,
                "endChar": 169,
                "prob": 0.15779,
                "text": "Apple is looking at buying U.K. startup for $3 billion"
            }
        ],
        "text": "Apple is looking at buying U.K. startup for $1 billion.\r\nApple is looking at buying U.K. startup for $2 billion.\r\nApple is looking at buying U.K. startup for $3 billion."
    },
    {
        "sectionId": 2,
        "entities": [
            {
                "id": 0,
                "startChar": 0,
                "endChar": 5,
                "label": "ORG",
                "text": "Apple"
            },
            {
                "id": 1,
                "startChar": 27,
                "endChar": 31,
                "label": "GPE",
                "text": "U.K"
            },
            {
                "id": 2,
                "startChar": 44,
                "endChar": 54,
                "label": "MONEY",
                "text": "$1 billion"
            },
            {
                "id": 3,
                "startChar": 57,
                "endChar": 62,
                "label": "ORG",
                "text": "Apple"
            },
            {
                "id": 4,
                "startChar": 84,
                "endChar": 88,
                "label": "GPE",
                "text": "U.K"
            },
            {
                "id": 5,
                "startChar": 101,
                "endChar": 111,
                "label": "MONEY",
                "text": "$1 billion"
            },
            {
                "id": 6,
                "startChar": 114,
                "endChar": 119,
                "label": "ORG",
                "text": "Apple"
            },
            {
                "id": 7,
                "startChar": 141,
                "endChar": 145,
                "label": "GPE",
                "text": "U.K"
            },
            {
                "id": 8,
                "startChar": 158,
                "endChar": 168,
                "label": "MONEY",
                "text": "$1 billion"
            }
        ],
        "sents": [
            {
                "id": 0,
                "startChar": 0,
                "endChar": 57,
                "prob": 0.43119,
                "text": "Apple is looking at buying U.K. startup for $1 billion."
            },
            {
                "id": 1,
                "startChar": 57,
                "endChar": 114,
                "prob": 0.22251,
                "text": "Apple is looking at buying U.K. startup for $2 billion"
            },
            {
                "id": 2,
                "startChar": 114,
                "endChar": 169,
                "prob": 0.15779,
                "text": "Apple is looking at buying U.K. startup for $3 billion"
            }
        ],
        "text": "Apple is looking at buying U.K. startup for $1 billion.\r\nApple is looking at buying U.K. startup for $2 billion.\r\nApple is looking at buying U.K. startup for $3 billion."
    }
]